CHRISTOPHER GLINKA

CONTACT

Edmonton
Canada
5877788210
glinkachris@gmail.com

SKILLS

- > Communication
- > Team Leadership
- > Mentoring
- > Project Management
- > HTML
- > CSS
- > JavaScript
- > React
- > Bootstrap
- > MUI
- > Flutter/Dart.js
- > Node.js
- > C#
- > .NET Core
- > Ling
- > SQL
- > Python

SUMMARY

Aspiring and enthusiastic Fullstack Developer with 3 years of technical education at NAIT's DMIT program. A natural team player that can also flourish in a team leadership role. Known for his charisma, reliability, flexibility, adaptability, consistency, and ability to effectively delegate tasks and problem-solve on the spot.

EXPERIENCE

Director of Education, Code Ninjas, St. Albert | October 2021 - Present

Teaches children ages 6-15 about coding concepts based on an evolving curriculum, starting with block coding, transitioning to JavaScript and eventually Lua, C#, and Unity game engine.

- Assisted on the Code Ninjas Windermere team that broke multiple company-wide records for customer acquisition and retention, making it the most successful and profitable location world-wide.
- Leadership role on the Code Ninjas St. Albert team that broke more records for a single location's grande opening. 70+ student sign ups prior to opening day, then breaking-even and surpassing 120 active accounts within 3 months of operation.
- Successfully constructed and taught multiple curriculums for various summer camps, including Web Development, beginner and intermediate Roblox Studio Development, Lego robotics, and 3D modelling and printing.

Barista, Starbucks, Edmonton | July 2021 - November 2021

- Created a wide variety of hot and cold beverages with consistently positive customer satisfaction scores.
- Successfully recommended products based on a deep understanding of customer needs and preferences.

Senior Sales Associate & Key-holder, GameStop, St.Albert | 2014 - 2020

- Trained new sales personnel on company policies, customer acquisition and retention strategies, and successful sales techniques.
- Met or exceeded sales objectives (weekly average of 80%+ warranty attachment) on a consistent basis to drive company growth.

EDUCATION

Northern Alberta Institute of Technology | DMIT, 2020 - Present

Studying Computer Software Development with an emphasis on Full Stack Development.

- Dean's Honour Roll 2021 & 2022
- Worked on a team of 3 other software developers to create a mock web application for a motorcycle shop's backend system from the ground up.
 We used the .NET Core framework with C# to build the backend business logic that stores, retrieves, and updates data from the database with an intuitive and accessible frontend UI/UX. The project can be viewed on my GitHub profile under eBike-WebApp.

Concordia University of Edmonton | Bachelor of Arts, 2016 - 2020

Graduated with a major in English and minor in Psychology.

 Excelled in group research projects that present data and important information in an accessible and concise manner, both written and presentation format.